A Guide to the General Files from the Office of the Dean of Students 1977-2007
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
General Files from the Office of the Dean of Students 1977-2007
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/2/1.092
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions apply under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.)
Acquisition Information
The papers were an archival transfer from the Office of the Dean Students, 2009 February 4.
Scope and Content
Topics include diversity, the Ernest H. Ern Award, the Gray-Carrington Memorial Foundation, fraternities and sororities, the Gus Blagden [Room] Committee, the Lawn Organizing Committee, the Lawn Selection Committee, leadership, the Stillfried-Godsey Memorial Scholarship, and the Women's Leadership Development Program.
Contents List
- Series I: General Files of the Papers of the Dean of Students, (674 items)
  - 1988-1991 Biennial Evaluation Report and Planning, (10 items) (Box-folder 1:1)
  - 1997-2000 Board of Visitors Greek Presentation, regarding IFC Rush, (30 items) (Box-folder 1:2)
  - 1990-1998 "Brief Biographical Sketches…" Report by Chester R. Titus, (5 items) (Box-folder 1:3)
  - 1976-1999 Building Names, (12 items) (Box-folder 1:4)
  - 1994-2000 Charting Diversity, (40 items) (Box-folder 1:5)
  - 2001 Mar Charting Diversity - Recommendations, (14 items) (Box-folder 1:6)
  - 2000 Feb Charting Diversity - Workshop Packet, (10 items) (Box-folder 1:7)
  - 2003-2005 Ernest H. Ern Award, (35 items) (Box-folder 1:8)
  - 2000 Fraternity Working Group, (51 items) (Box-folder 2:1)
  - 1993-2001 Gray-Carrington Memorial Foundation, (16 items) (Box-folder 2:2)
  - 2002-2005 Gray-Carrington Memorial Foundation, (35 items) (Box-folder 2:3)
  - 1997-1999 Greek Affairs, (34 items) (Box-folder 2:4)
  - 2000 Greek Affairs, (33 items) (Box-folder 2:5)
  - 2003-2005 Gus Blagden Committee, (45 items) (Box-folder 2:6)
  - 1977-1999 Intern List, of Dean Canevari, items) (Box-folder 2:7)
  - 2005 Feb Lawn Appeal, (11 items) (Box-folder 2:8)
  - 2003-2004 Lawn Organizing Committee, (55 items) (Box-folder 2:9)
  - 2004-2007 Lawn Organizing Committee, (43 items) (Box-folder 3:1)
  - 1988; 2001-2002 Lawn Selection Committee, (47 items) (Box-folder 3:2)
  - 2003-2005 Lawn Selection Committee, (14 items) (Box-folder 3:3)
  - 2002 Leadership 2002, (28 items) (Box-folder 3:4)
  - 2003 Jun Leadership 2003, items) (Box-folder 3:5)
  - 2004 Leadership 2004, (3 items) (Box-folder 3:6)
  - 2005 Leadership 2005, (1 item) (Box-folder 3:7)
  - [1818 Aug 4] Rockfish Gap Report - Computer Print-out Copy, (1 item) (Box-folder 3:8)
  - 2002-2004 Stillfried-Godsey Memorial Scholarship, (35 items) (Box-folder 3:9)
  - 2001 Women's Leadership Development Program, (2 items) (Box-folder 3:10)
  - 2002 Women's Leadership Development Program, (22 items) (Box-folder 3:11)
- Series II: Restricted Files of the Papers of the Dean of Students, (144 items)
  - 2004-2005 Ernest H. Ern Award, (19 items) (Box-folder 4:1)
  - 2003-2005 Gray-Carrington Memorial Foundation, (100 items) (Box-folder 4:2)
  - 2004-2007 Lawn Organizing Committee, (3 items) (Box-folder 4:3)
  - 2002-2005 Stillfried-Godsey Memorial Scholarship, (22 items) (Box-folder 4:4)